Stories live forever. People don't
The Ballad of Buster Scruggs is a western, comedy,
drama film directed by Joel Coen.
Vignettes weaving together the stories of six individuals in
the old West at the end of the Civil War.
Following the tales of a sharp-shooting songster, a wannabe bank robber, two weary traveling performers, a lone gold prospector,
a woman traveling the West to an uncertain future, and a motley crew of strangers undertaking a carriage ride.
Buster Scruggs (segment "The Ballad of Buster
Scruggs"), played by Tim Blake Nelson.
The Kid (segment "The Ballad of Buster Scruggs"), played by Willie Watson.
Curly Joe (segment "The Ballad of Buster Scruggs"), played by Clancy Brown.
Curly Joe's Brother (segment "The Ballad of Buster
Scruggs"), played by Danny McCarthy.
Frenchman (segment "The Ballad of Buster Scruggs"), played by David Krumholtz.
Gun Check Man (segment "The Ballad of Buster
Scruggs"), played by Thomas Wingate.
The Ballad of Buster Scruggs (titled on-screen as The Ballad of Buster Scruggs and Other Tales of the American Frontier) is a
2018 American Western black comedy anthology film written, directed, produced, and edited by the Coen brothers.
It stars Tim Blake Nelson, Tyne Daly, James Franco, Brendan Gleeson, Bill Heck, Grainger Hines, Zoe
Kazan, Harry Melling, Liam Neeson, Jonjo O'Neill, Chelcie Ross, Saul Rubinek, and Tom Waits.
It consists of six vignettes set on the American frontier.
The film premiered at the 75th Venice International Film Festival on August 31,
2018, where it won the Golden Osella Award for Best Screenplay.
After a limited theatrical run beginning on November 9, 2018,
it was released on Netflix on November 16.
The National Board of Review named it one of its top ten films of 2018.
The film earned three nominations at the 91st Academy Awards: Best Adapted Screenplay, Best
Costume Design, and Best Original Song ("When a Cowboy Trades His Spurs for Wings").
The film explores themes of prostitute, native
american, parody, anthology, bank robbery.
The tone is lighthearted and emotional and mind_bending.